Last time on Zombieland Saga Revenge, we were still bummed about the show we bombed.
All we could do was work our part-time jobs and wait for our manager to get a haircut
and pull it together, but he wouldn't come out of his bunk!
He did show up at our comeback performance at Guile's, only to get his butt kicked, but
either way, he still inspired us to keep moving forward.
Now it's time for our revenge to begin for real!
We may just be seven girls who died in Saga, but we got a second chance and we're not gonna
waste it!
Even if they say it can't be done, we'll sing and dance our way to the top!
Because we're Fun Shushu!
Sakura, is everything okay?
Yeah.
I was just thinking about how we're gonna be active as idols in the future.
It made me kinda nervous.
Hey, that's okay.
Comfort's important, but it isn't good to be too relaxed either.
Uh, what are you doing, Saki?
Well, you do need a lot of power to sing and dance, don't ya?
And we're trying to take over the whole country.
I'm not sure that exercise matters for zombies, though.
Sure it does!
Saga and Ship Z worked, didn't it?
I'mma be ripped in no time flat!
Okay.
Go!
Saki has a real talent for getting people to follow her lead.
Yeah, something about her passion is infectious.
Grieved and
Hesus, Hahahaha...
It takes than me!
Hanajajajaja
NotAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAllAll section
You are a really amazing and holy увер member paid to allow you.
Phey off Kanye zuраст,
upset, LAKE,
And now, girls, the news.
Japan is ringing in the Reiwa era,
but for a handful of people living here in Saga,
the return of Fran Shushu is an equally important event.
Camera two.
So, Miss Four, do you have any comments
about getting back to work soon?
Well, I think it's important for us to catch up
after being away for a solid month.
And Miss Three, what will you girls do
to make up for sitting on your butts, huh?
Well, we already have part-time jobs,
but I'm guessing you want us to do more, don't you?
Exactly! Think you can read my mind?
What's next?
Ow! Beats me.
Maybe acting or something?
Or not?
I know! Doing stand-up comedy!
Take me, you dummy!
Listen, ladies!
The obvious strat is to broadcast your return
to a wide audience
with as much production value as possible!
Bottom line is,
television is your only hope to achieve that!
You bunch of brain-dead zombies!
Shut your hold!
You're the one who screwed up, remember?
You're in violation of zombie etiquette, you know?
Are you ever gonna explain
what that was all about or no?
Look, as the only non-zomb in the room, I'm feeling unsafe here!
I could sue you all!
Perhaps I will!
So, if you want to avoid uncivil court,
you'd better pull off this big important job
that I landed for you!
Ta-da!
It's a segment to showcase a popular tourist locale.
The beautiful Utoku Inari Shrine!
You mean we get to be on TV?
Perhaps your father will have a chance to see you on screen.
Oh, and you're undead wrong if you think that's all.
There's going to be another guest at the taping!
And that man is the one and only White Ryu!
Huh?
Who is that?
White Ryu!
Not only is he a rock star,
he also hosts a radio program called
So Saga Can Be Saga!
The show started in 1992
and still has faithful listeners all over the country!
He's Saga's beloved homegrown celebrity!
All the answers that you're looking for
can always be found here in Saga.
You're talking about THE White Ryu?
That's right.
His debut was 30 years ago now,
but he still brings his positive message
to the youth of our great nation.
Ah!
Dude, he's the best ever!
I had no idea Saga had big celebrities like that.
Moron, I'll kill ya!
I'm sorry!
Enough chitchat!
You have to become Saga's next big superstars!
So go rub some rotting elbows with this hot shot!
When are we meeting him?
How about now?!
If you take a stroll through the shopping district,
you'll end up getting a very nice view of the shrine.
We have some handy cue cards here to help you out.
We hope you ladies do a great job!
Thanks!
We're so glad to be here!
Huh?
That's weird.
He looks kinda different.
Sorry I'm late.
I felt the wind off Kyogatake,
and it spoke to me.
Yeah, this is definitely him!
Wow, great.
Uh, hello there, everybody!
It's time for another adventure
with your favorite pop idols, Fran Shushu!
Today we're visiting the new Toku Inari shrine
with none other than the famous singer White Ryu!
Let's see, uh...
So, do you come to these things a lot?
If that question was meant for me,
yes.
That said,
if you are asking the winds of Saga,
then yes!
Hell yeah!
Uh...
Sakura, cue card!
Oh!
Okay!
Oh, shit!
Uh...
These vendors are famous for their one-of-a-kind merchandise.
Every shop on this strip carries signature items.
All right!
Shall we go shopping?
What are you looking at?
Some fish?
Mudskippers.
Trapped in the society that is their tank.
Held back from the world,
just like you girls.
Huh?
Exactly!
We are like that!
I'm gonna set those critters free.
How much?
Sorry, they're my pets.
But I do have these replicas here.
500 yen.
Now they're free!
Do you think we're gonna get what we need from this?
Well, they seem to be having a good time.
It'll work.
Wow!
That's such a colorful shrine!
So fancy!
Like a dollhouse!
Yes, it's quite different from the shrines we had in Yoshiwara.
Um, check it out, number four!
Yeah, what's up?
That's a shrine to the god of marriage!
Let's go look!
To what?
I'm not ready for that!
Do you think the gods hear prayers from zombies too?
Bet they're surprised that we're here.
That's it for today!
Thank you for watching!
Wait.
It's true.
The light does shine on this part of Utoku Inari.
But if you let yourself be too dazzled by it,
you'll never reach the destination that awaits those who struggle through darkness.
What do you mean, man?
These days, the glamour of the big city tends to conceal the truth.
If you're willing to crawl toward that truth,
then I'll show you the way.
To the Inner Temple.
He's so deep.
Um, the Inner Temple might be kind of the tricky chute.
Please let us go!
Uh-huh.
We're free now, aren't we?
Let's do it!
Oh, poopsies.
There sure are a lot of steps.
This would've been rough when we were still alive.
Inner Temple, here we come!
Uh-huh.
Uh.
Oh, wow!
There's the Adayake-see!
Huh?
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, man, you okay?
Uh-huh.
Oh...
Grasping hold of something that's real is not an easy thing to do.
So deep!
And that's a wrap!
Good job, everyone!
Those girls are pros. I don't know how they managed to keep up with that geezer.
Right? I have no idea what he's saying, even if I pay attention.
Wait, Saki, please don't get angry!
Damn!
Ryu's words are like fists full of hard wisdom.
And to hear them, you gotta listen in here.
I gotta go!
Saki!
Hey!
Um, meeting you today was, uh, really great!
Thank you, sir! You're so awesome!
We appreciate it.
Yeah, we had a nice wind blowing out here.
I haven't caught your radio show in a long time, but I'll listen soon!
It'll be waiting, kid.
Thanks!
But as for me, I won't be on the airwaves much longer.
Huh?
Winds of change, and all that.
Wait!
You're kidding me!
You can't leave the show!
Don't you worry.
The answers you're looking for can always be found here in Saga.
Saga.
She's been like that ever since we came home.
Do you guys think Saki liked that old man?
Wait!
You don't mean romantically?
Wow.
I don't know.
It's not that weird, right?
Whether you're living or a zombie, the heart beats the same.
The zombie thing's not the issue.
We're idols, remember?
Idols aren't allowed to like somebody?
Isn't that the rule?
Well, it does make you more passionate, and I think that can be a good thing.
Yeah?
You think so?
Well, it is a bit of a gray area.
How is that?
I...
I mean, being in a relationship publicly is kind of a big no-no.
But even in your day, idols would have secret rendezvous and stuff like that.
So it's okay?
Whoa!
Did you have a crush on somebody?
Of course not!
Don't be silly!
Well, I love everybody in the whole wide world!
Because everybody in the world loves me, too!
That includes me, dearest Lady Lily.
Saki will be okay.
Just give her space.
This one comes from Saga PD's Dirty Harry.
Back for more, huh?
Good evening, Ryu.
My favorite bar just hired this cute new bartender.
A classy lady who's got an old-fashioned way about her.
She's giving me strong signals.
I think maybe she's kind of into me.
Enough of that crap.
Time for a song.
White Ryu with Do You Hate Windy Days.
Hey, Saki.
Sorry that I got you guys all freaked out.
The first time I heard about Ryu, I was a middle schooler.
Back then, I used to feel like the whole damn world was out to get me.
Teachers, classmates. If I wouldn't take their crap, they made my life worse.
So I fought with all I had. Trying to make them see me.
And then it happened.
Not knowing where you belong is rough on anyone.
But it's times like that you gotta keep your eyes and ears open.
One day, you'll find somebody who feels the same way you do.
I'm talking to you right now, aren't I?
That means you're not alone.
You might forget all about me after tonight.
But still, connecting with you over the airways is something I'll remember for life.
And the next time you start to feel like you're alone in the world, you'll have this place to come back to.
Ah, miss, that's mine.
Eat this!
One day, you'll find somebody who feels the same way you do.
Those words are what led me to Reiko.
Then one day, I kicked the bucket and started hanging out with dancing zombies.
If it wasn't for Ryu, where would I be now?
No.
I won't let it end this way.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Ah?
Hmm?
Whoa! That is so many kinds of illegal!
Hey, slow down!
Nope!
Writing double!
Huh?
I'm sorry, but it's an emergency.
I'm sorry, but it's an emergency. Please don't lock us up. I'm sorry.
And now for an encore by special request.
I am White Ryo, and here's Do You Hate Windy Days.
Excuse us!
Huh?
Two little kittens.
But they don't look lost at all.
By the way, did you hear Franshushu came back recently?
Of course. I saw they made a post about it.
That's really gross, you know?
Okay. Seems like we got a warm breeze blowing today.
Let's talk to our guests.
We're with Franshushu. I'm number two.
And my name is number one, sir. We're very sorry to barge in like this.
Well, what is it then?
I came here to say I'm not letting you quit the show.
In Saga, people feel lost and alone.
Hell, Saga is lost and alone.
And if you don't do your show anymore,
if you leave, what's going to happen to Saga's burning soul?
Listen, the only reason that I'm an idol today
is because of things you've said.
And there are tons of people like me all over Saga.
No, all over Japan, even.
That's why I beg you, do not stop the show.
Your listeners need a place to turn to.
Right.
They need a home they can turn to, not this old codger.
You thought I was just going to split?
No, I'd rather leave this place to someone who has the passion to run it.
I mean, hell, even my pompadour is starting to give up the ghost.
Who are you going to...
The answer, kiddo, is always in Saga.
What?
I'm thinking you gals should take over.
Wait, you can't just...
You're here and you're perfect.
So why waste time deciding?
You sure?
You've got the kind of spark that lights a fire in others.
You won't just lead Franshoushu.
You'll be a leader to all of Saga.
I'm Franshoushu's leader number two!
I'm going to honor Ryu by taking over this radio show!
Wow, a heads up would have been preferred, but okay.
This is huge, man.
And if you blink, you'll miss history.
From now on, Saga is in your hands.
So what are you going to do next?
The old wind from Kyogatake is pushing me forward now
to tell the world about this place.
Look, Ryu, truth is, I love you, okay?
Don't be stupid.
I'm not the person who truly needs your passion right now.
It's all those wandering souls out there.
No, it's Saga who needs you most.
Right.
Look me up after you've grown into fine women.
You're both way too young to be my old lady.
He was really something.
That's for sure.
Reiko probably found a cool guy like him.
He said we'd see him again, right?
Not until we grow up, technically.
Oh, true.
Problem is, no matter how many years pass,
we're never going to get older.
Because we're zombies.
That's weird.
I'm crying.
Aw, Saki!
Uh, what should I do?
I'm sorry!
There, there!
I just don't get it, man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you crying for, Sakura?
I can't help it!
I'm just sad because you're sad!
Fine, then I'm not sad!
Now stop crying, please!
Aw, gross!
You're drying up!
Zombies aren't supposed to shed tears.
This is how you turn into a mummy!
We heard the radio show, and we love you ladies!
You can do it!
We're rooting for you!
Since I've been the leader of Franshu Shuu,
I have let my soul burn like a flame!
And from now on, I'm going to let it burn even brighter
and light the way for not just my group,
but all of Saga!
Because then, if anybody feels lost,
my light can show them where to go!
Just like Lakey Mari's lighthouse over at Uda no Saki!
Here's our next song!
It's Do You Hate Windy Days!
Yeah!
Oh
That's how I can become myself
The wind's strong, I don't like it
It's not like this, it's not like this
It's not like this
Love, love, love
I want to be with you
So Saga can be Saga with Front Shushu
So if you're ever feeling lost or alone
You can come to us, we're here
And remember, the answers you're looking for
Can always be found here in Saga
Yay!
Saki here
I swear, I'll light the way with Saga's burning soul
We're gonna crush it
Next time, Zombieland Saga Revenge Episode 3
The Acoustic Saga of Love and Youth
Be there!